(this.webpackJsonpstrooptest=this.webpackJsonpstrooptest||[]).push([[0],{26:function(e,t,r){},27:function(e,t,r){},34:function(e,t,r){"use strict";r.r(t);var s=r(0),n=r.n(s),o=r(13),c=r.n(o),i=(r(26),r(27),r(12)),a=r(3),l=r(5),x=r(48),w=r(2);var T=function(){var e=Object(a.e)(),t=Object(s.useState)("none"),r=Object(l.a)(t,2),n=r[0],o=r[1],c=Object(s.useState)("none"),i=Object(l.a)(c,2);return i[0],i[1],Object(w.jsx)("div",{className:"app1",children:Object(w.jsxs)("div",{className:"card",children:[Object(w.jsx)("p",{className:"title",children:"Stroop Test "}),Object(w.jsx)("label",{children:"choose a level:"}),Object(w.jsxs)("select",{name:"level",placeholder:n,onChange:function(e){o(e.target.value)},className:"select",children:[Object(w.jsx)("option",{value:"none",className:"select",children:" None "}),Object(w.jsx)("option",{value:"low",className:"select",children:" Easy "}),Object(w.jsx)("option",{value:"high",className:"select",children:" Advanced "})]}),Object(w.jsx)("div",{className:"but",children:Object(w.jsx)(x.a,{variant:"outlined",onClick:function(){console.log(n),"low"==n?(localStorage.setItem("level","low"),e.push("/text")):"high"==n&&(localStorage.setItem("level","high"),e.push("/text"))},color:"primary",children:"Start"})}),"   "]})})},u=[{questionText:"RED",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"BLUE",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"GREEN",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"BLUE",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"GREEN",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"YELLOW",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"BLUE",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"GREEN",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"YELLOW",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"RED",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"GREEN",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"YELLOW",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"RED",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"BLUE",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"GREEN",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"RED",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!1}]}];r(20);var j=function(){localStorage.clear(),Object(a.e)();var e=u,t=Object(s.useState)("yellow"),r=Object(l.a)(t,2),n=r[0],o=r[1],c=Object(s.useState)(0),T=Object(l.a)(c,2),j=T[0],C=T[1],d=Object(s.useState)(!1),O=Object(l.a)(d,2),h=O[0],b=O[1],p=Object(s.useState)(0),m=Object(l.a)(p,2),v=m[0],f=m[1],R=Object(s.useState)(30),E=Object(l.a)(R,2),g=E[0],B=E[1],G=Object(s.useState)(0),Y=Object(l.a)(G,2),q=(Y[0],Y[1],function(t){t&&f(v+1);var r=j+1;r<e.length?(e[j+1].answerOptions.map((function(e){if(1==e.isCorrect)return o(e.answerText.toLowerCase()),e.answerText.toLowerCase()})),C(r)):b(!0)});return Object(s.useEffect)((function(){localStorage.getItem("home")||g>0&&setTimeout((function(){return B(g-1)}),1e3)}),[g]),Object(w.jsx)("div",{className:"app",children:h||!g?Object(w.jsxs)("div",{className:"score-section",children:[Object(w.jsxs)("span",{children:["You scored ",v," out of ",e.length]}),localStorage.setItem("home",1),Object(w.jsxs)(i.b,{to:"/",children:[Object(w.jsx)("br",{})," ",Object(w.jsx)(x.a,{variant:"contained",color:"primary",onClick:function(){localStorage.removeItem("home")},children:"Home"})]})]}):Object(w.jsxs)(w.Fragment,{children:[Object(w.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-section",children:[Object(w.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-count",children:[Object(w.jsxs)("span",{children:["Question ",j+1]}),"/",e.length,Object(w.jsx)("br",{}),Object(w.jsx)("br",{}),Object(w.jsxs)("span",{children:["Timer : ",g]})]}),Object(w.jsx)("div",{className:"question-text",style:{color:n},children:e[j].questionText})]}),Object(w.jsx)("div",{className:"answer-section",children:e[j].answerOptions.map((function(e){return Object(w.jsxs)("button",{onClick:function(){q(e.isCorrect)},children:[" ",e.answerText]})}))})]})})},C=[{questionText:"RED",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"BLUE",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"GREEN",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"BLUE",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"GREEN",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"YELLOW",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"BLUE",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"GREEN",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"YELLOW",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"RED",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"GREEN",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"YELLOW",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"RED",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"BLUE",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!1}]},{questionText:"GREEN",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!0}]},{questionText:"RED",answerOptions:[{answerText:"Red",isCorrect:!0},{answerText:"Blue",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Yellow",isCorrect:!1},{answerText:"Green",isCorrect:!1}]}];var d=function(){localStorage.clear(),Object(a.e)();var e=C,t=Object(s.useState)("red"),r=Object(l.a)(t,2),n=r[0],o=r[1],c=Object(s.useState)(0),T=Object(l.a)(c,2),u=T[0],j=T[1],d=Object(s.useState)(!1),O=Object(l.a)(d,2),h=O[0],b=O[1],p=Object(s.useState)(0),m=Object(l.a)(p,2),v=m[0],f=m[1],R=Object(s.useState)(30),E=Object(l.a)(R,2),g=E[0],B=E[1],G=Object(s.useState)(0),Y=Object(l.a)(G,2),q=(Y[0],Y[1],function(t){t&&f(v+1);var r=u+1;r<e.length?(e[u+1].answerOptions.map((function(e){if(1==e.isCorrect)return o(e.answerText.toLowerCase()),e.answerText.toLowerCase()})),j(r)):b(!0)});return Object(s.useEffect)((function(){localStorage.getItem("home")||g>0&&setTimeout((function(){return B(g-1)}),1e3)}),[g]),Object(w.jsx)("div",{className:"app",children:h||!g?Object(w.jsxs)("div",{className:"score-section",children:[Object(w.jsxs)("span",{children:["You scored ",v," out of ",e.length]}),localStorage.setItem("home",1),Object(w.jsxs)(i.b,{to:"/",children:[Object(w.jsx)("br",{})," ",Object(w.jsx)(x.a,{variant:"contained",color:"primary",onClick:function(){localStorage.removeItem("home")},children:"Home"})]})]}):Object(w.jsxs)(w.Fragment,{children:[Object(w.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-section",children:[Object(w.jsxs)("div",{className:"question-count",children:[Object(w.jsxs)("span",{children:["Question ",u+1]}),"/",e.length,Object(w.jsx)("br",{}),Object(w.jsx)("br",{}),Object(w.jsxs)("span",{children:["Timer : ",g]})]}),Object(w.jsx)("div",{className:"question-text",style:{color:n},children:e[u].questionText})]}),Object(w.jsx)("div",{className:"answer-section",children:e[u].answerOptions.map((function(e){return Object(w.jsxs)("button",{onClick:function(){q(e.isCorrect)},children:[" ",e.answerText]})}))})]})})};var O=function(){var e=Object(a.e)(),t=localStorage.getItem("level");return Object(w.jsxs)("div",{className:"app3",children:[Object(w.jsxs)("p",{children:[Object(w.jsx)("h3",{children:"Stroop Effect:"}),"The Stroop effect is one of the best known phenomena in cognitive psychology. The Stroop effect occurs when people do the Stroop task, which is explained and demonstrated in detail in this lesson. The Stroop effect is related to selective attention, which is the ability to respond to certain environmental stimuli while ignoring others."]}),Object(w.jsxs)("p",{children:[Object(w.jsx)("h3",{children:"Stroop Test Task:"}),"In this task There will be two test levels those are Easy and Advance, In Easy level test people simply look at colour words, such as blue, red, or green. In Advance level takes longer time and is more prone to errors where the colour of the ink does not match the name of the colour. which makes people under stress and helps to check people attention."]}),Object(w.jsxs)("p",{children:[Object(w.jsx)("h3",{children:"Instructions:"}),"There will be 16 words in each level you should choose colour of the word not what the word actually it is,After choosing the colour of word for next word will be presented which has to be chosen, You will have 30 seconds to complete each level,Your score and time taken to complete tells your attention."]}),Object(w.jsx)("div",{className:"but",children:Object(w.jsx)(x.a,{variant:"outlined",onClick:function(){"low"==t?e.push("/test2"):"high"==t&&e.push("/test1")},className:"textbutton",color:"primary",children:"Start"})})]})};var h=function(){return Object(w.jsxs)(i.a,{children:[Object(w.jsx)(a.a,{exact:!0,path:"/",children:Object(w.jsx)(T,{})}),Object(w.jsx)(a.a,{exact:!0,path:"/test1",children:Object(w.jsx)(j,{})}),Object(w.jsx)(a.a,{exact:!0,path:"/test2",children:Object(w.jsx)(d,{})}),Object(w.jsx)(a.a,{exact:!0,path:"/text",children:Object(w.jsx)(O,{})})]})},b=function(e){e&&e instanceof Function&&r.e(3).then(r.bind(null,49)).then((function(t){var r=t.getCLS,s=t.getFID,n=t.getFCP,o=t.getLCP,c=t.getTTFB;r(e),s(e),n(e),o(e),c(e)}))};c.a.render(Object(w.jsx)(n.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(w.jsx)(h,{})}),document.getElementById("root")),b()}},[[34,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.bb48d5d9.chunk.js.map